那么 JavaScript 在哪里运行呢？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Where does
JavaScript actually run?
它在哪里运行代码？
Where is it running its code?
彼得，JavaScript 在哪里运行？
Peter, where's JavaScript running?
通常是在浏览器中。
&gt;&gt; Peter: Typically in a browser.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 在浏览器中,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: In the browser,
是啊，我们不开一个叫 JavaScript 的应用，对吧？
yeah, we don't open an app
called JavaScript, right?
我们在打开的浏览器中运行它，现在浏览器是一个了不起的创造。
We, run it in a browser we turn on,
now the browser is a remarkable creation.
它不仅仅包含了 JavaScript，所以让我们,
It has so much more than just
JavaScript in it, so let's just,
我们在这里使用一支白色的笔作为 JavaScript 引擎。
we use a white pen here for
the JavaScript engine.
作为蓝色的一部分，整个网页浏览器,
As part of the blue,
the overall web browser,
比如说，我不会画 Firefox。
sort of say is, I can't draw the Firefox.
这就是 JavaScript，它不是孤立运行的，它有大量的特性
There it is JavaScript, it doesn't run
in isolation, it has a ton of features
浏览器的其他特性是什么？
in the web browser as well, what are the
other features that the web browser has?
亚当，你能想到网页浏览器的其他特性吗
Adam, can you think of some other features
the web browser has that JavaScript
没有吗？
does not have?
亚当: 比如开发工具？
&gt;&gt; Adam: Like dev tools?
威尔 · 森特斯: 当然，是的，绝对的，老实说，是的，开发工具,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Sure, yeah,
absolutely, honestly, yeah, dev tools,
让我们把它放在开发工具，控制台，是的，绝对的，还有什么其他的东西，马特？
let's put it in dev tools, console, yeah,
absolutely, what other things, Matt?
Matt: Web sockets？
&gt;&gt; Matt: Web sockets?
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，当然，套接字。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, sure, sockets.
威尔: 还有什么？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: What other thing?
有一些非常关键，两个非常关键，丹，你有一个吗？
There are some really key,
two really key ones, Dan, you got one?
能和互联网对话吗？
Can Javascript speak to the Internet?
它能通过因特网发出网络请求吗？
Can it make network
requests over the Internet?
不 JavaScript 不具备与互联网对话的能力,
No, JavaScript does not have
the ability to speak to the Internet,
这不是 JavaScript 的一个特性。
that is not a feature inside JavaScript.
所以你知道吗，浏览器是这样的,
So you know what,
the browser does, though,
浏览器可以发出网络请求。
the browser can make network requests.
浏览器是一个令人难以置信的应用程序，它充满了所有这些，它是一个复合体
The browser is this incredible app, that's
full of all of these, it's a composite
一个 JavaScript 引擎，加上大量的非 JavaScript 特性。
of a JavaScript engine that this bit,
plus a ton of non-JavaScript features.
其中之一就是它发出网络请求的能力,
One of which is the ability for
it to make network requests,
还有什么东西是 JavaScript 绝对没有的？
what other thing does
JavaScript definitely not have?
马特: 渲染。
&gt;&gt; Matt: Rendering.
是的，渲染，确切地说，是用 JavaScript 实现的吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, rendering,
exactly, is that in JavaScript?
不那是在网页浏览器里我们的 HTML DOM,
No, that's in the web browser,
our HTML DOM,
这就是我们的模型，我们简化版的纸上内容。
that is our model, our simplified
version of what's on the page.
这是我们在页面上的简化版本
That's our simplified version
of what's on the page so
我们可以和它互动，这样我们就可以在页面上添加东西。
that we can interact with it, so
we can add stuff to that page.
文档对象模型，它是一个模型，一个对象的简化版本
Document Object Model, it's a model,
a simplified version in an object
文档的样式格式，也就是页面的视觉效果。
style format of what's on the document,
which is the visual of the page.
所有这些我们不能直接编码的功能,
Yeah, all these features we
cannot code for directly,
不管浏览器是用什么写的，它们都是用 c + + 写的。
they're written in whatever
the browser is written, in C++.
或者其他语言的浏览器,
Or whatever other languages,
the browser is written in,
我们直接写这些吗？
do we write for these directly?
但是人们，我们确实有一种编程语言，可以让我们使用这些特性。
But people, we do have a programming
language that lets us use these features.
这种编程语言是 JavaScript，但我们不会
And that programming language is
JavaScript, but we're not actually gonna
在 JavaScript 中找到这些特性，那么我们如何与它们交互呢？
find any of these features in JavaScript,
so how do we interact with them?
我们如何与它们交互？
How do we interface with them?
在 JavaScript 中，我们得到了一些我称之为 facade 函数的东西
In JavaScript we get a bunch of
what I call facade functions, and
我说清楚了，这不流行。
it's not catching on, I'll be clear.
这个短语并没有流行起来，我把它们叫做正面
This phrase is not catching on, a bunch
of what's called, I call them facade
这些函数看起来像是 JavaScript。
functions, they are functions that
look like they're JavaScript.
但是实际上是网页浏览器功能的正面，正面，你知道吗？
But are actually fronts, facades, for
web browser features and you know what?
其中一个浏览器功能信不信由你,
One of those web browser
features believe it or not,
甚至没有 web 浏览器中的定时器功能。
JavaScript doesn't even have the feature
of a timer that's in the web browser too.
我们得到了这些功能的标签,
And we get labels for
each of these features,
希望和名字完全一致，那会很好，对吧？
let's hope are perfectly aligned to
the name, that'll be very nice, right?
如果它们与名称完全对齐,
If they were perfectly
aligned to the name instead,
凯拉你觉得我们定时器的标签是什么？
Kayla what do you think our label for
timer would be?
定时器？
&gt;&gt; Kayla: Timer?
威尔 · 森坦斯: 这个名字很有道理，是个完美的名字，但在现实中,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: That makes sense, that
would be a perfect name, but in reality,
我们在 JavaScript 中使用什么标签来启动计时器来延迟函数
what label do we get in JavaScript in
order to start a timer to delay a function
凯拉？
Kayla?
设定时间。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: Set time out.
威尔 · 森特斯: 设定时间，就是这样，设定时间不是做什么
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Set time out,
that's it, set time out is not doing
所有在 JavaScript 中感兴趣的东西都是一个标签
anything of interest in JavaScript
instead it's a label for
网页浏览器上的定时器。
the timer built to the web browser.
Braden，HTML DOM 的标签是什么，希望是 DOM，对吗？
Braden, what's our label for the HTML DOM,
hopefully it's like DOM, right?
布雷顿: 那太好了。
&gt;&gt; Braydon: That would be nice.
威尔 · 森特斯: 那太好了，那是什么呢？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: That'd be nice,
what is it instead?
布雷顿: 我不知道。
&gt;&gt; Braydon: I don't know.
Will Sentance: 当我们想要使用 JavaScript 的时候，我们有什么样的标签呢
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Well, what label do we
have in JavaScript whenever we wanna use
一种允许我们显示的网页浏览器特性的集合，以及
a kind of collection of features of the
web browser that allow us to display, and
渲染，并在页面上显示东西？
render, and display stuff on the page?
彼得: 文件。
&gt;&gt; Peter: Document.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 文件，彼得的观点正确。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Document,
Peter's spot on.
没错，文档，所以每当你看到文档,
Exactly, Document, so
whenever you see Document,
在 JavaScript 中什么也做不了。
that ain't doing anything in JavaScript.
这是一个使用网页浏览器特性的命令，这有点疯狂。
It's a command to go and use a feature of
the web browser, that's kind of crazy.
托德，我们对网络特征的定义是什么
Todd, what do we have as our label for
the feature of the web
浏览器，让我们做网络请求对互联网说话？
browser that lets us do network
request speaking to the Internet?
有人知道吗？
Anyone know?
你知道吗？
Dan you know?
阿丹: 是吗？
&gt;&gt; Dan: Is it get?
威尔 · 森塔斯: 不完全是，那是我们过去常用的,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Not quite,
that's the one which we used to kind of,
那是特写的包装纸。
that was a wrapper for the feature.
Tcp UDP.
&gt;&gt; Dan: TCP UDP.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 我们有什么 Tcp UDP.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: What did we have?
&gt;&gt; Dan: TCP UDP.
威尔 · 桑塔斯: 不是直接的。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Not directly.
捡回来？
&gt;&gt; Kayla: Fetch?
威尔 · 森坦斯: “取” ，凯拉的名字，是我们比较新的名字
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fetch, Kayla's spot on,
that's our sort of newer name for
但我们以前给它取了个不同的名字，大家还记得吗？
it, but we used to have a different
name for it, everyone remember?
阿贾克斯。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: AJAX.
威尔 · 森特斯: 不，是 xhr，大家还记得 xhr 吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: No, it was something
it was xhr, everyone remember xhr?
不过顺便说一句看看我们的名字和底层特征是多么一致,
Though, by the way, look how consistent
our names are with the underlying feature,
好吧控制台这个更合理一点,
okay, console,
this one's a little bit more reasonable,
控制台的标签是什么，杰夫？
what's the label for console, Jeff?
杰夫: 控制台。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Console.
威尔 · 森特斯: 控制台，抓住杰夫，太好了，杰夫完美地着陆了,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Console, hold on Jeff,
excellent, Jeff landed that perfectly,
我们还有其他特性，比如本地存储，IndexedDB，所有这些。
and we have other features here like
local storage, IndexedDB, all of those.
所以本地存储的名字是本地存储，所以他们随着时间的推移变得越来越好。
So local storage's name is local storage,
so they got better at it over time.
他们在 JavaScript 标签的命名上确实做得更好
They definitely got better at
naming the JavaScript label for
网页浏览器功能。
the web browser feature over time.
但在早期，我不知道它们是否是最聪明的。
But in the early days, I don't know
these were not the smartest, whatever.
好吧，乡亲们，这意味着我们的一大部分
Alright, so folk,
that means a big part of what we're
在 JavaScript 中所做的事情根本不是 JavaScript。
doing in JavaScript isn't
even JavaScript at all.
也就是说我需要在这里扩展我的 JavaScript 平台,
Meaning I'm gonna need to expand
my platform of JavaScript on here,
从 JavaScript 的三大部分开始。
taking it from being just those
big three pieces in JavaScript.
作为 JavaScript 的三大部分，加上,
Being the big three pieces in JavaScript,
plus,
我会把下面所有的东西都放在网页浏览器里。
I'm gonna have everything below here be
stuff that's happening in the web browser.
我要做蓝色，当你看到蓝色，它代表网页浏览器和
I'm gonna do in blue, and when you see
blue, it represents the web browser and
与 JavaScript 无关，好了，伙计们，我们开始吧。
not anything to do with JavaScript,
okay folks, here we go.
这是一个擦拭停机时间，所以转向你的伙伴，转向你的邻居和
It's a board wipe downtime, so turn to
your partner, turn to your neighbor and
开始尝试导航和用语言表达这些代码在做什么。
start trying to navigate and
verbalize what this code is doing.
试一试吧，我们还没有工具来做这件事，但是
Give it a shot, we don't have
the tools yet to do this, but
既然我们知道设置超时，那么它就是网页浏览器中计时器的标签。
given that we know set timeout, is gonna
be a label for timer in the web browser.
想想这里可能会发生什么，并且
Have a think what might be happening here,
and
好好想想该怎么解释布莱登。
have a think about how
one might explain Braden.
伊桑的直觉告诉我们这里的执行顺序是怎样的
And Ethan's instincts around what the
order of execution here might be, try and
走在它前面。
get ahead of it.